Julián Emanuel Poma

Rosario, Argentina / julianepoma@gmail.com / julianpoma.com

Julián is a **Software Engineer and Full Stack Web Developer** from Argentina. He has experience working with Laravel, Node.js and Vue.js. He loves being surrounded by great people, and working on projects that have a great chance to make an impact.

Experience

Node.js and MongoDB Developer - Whyline.

Rosario, January 2019 - Present

- Member of the mobile app team, in charge of giving support for new features and integrations in the backend used by more than 200k users.

Laravel 5 and Vue.js Developer - SGC S.A.

Rosario, December 2017 - January 2019

- In charge of the development of a lite-CRM system used to manage 5000 customers and the services offered.
- Launch an interacting site were potential customers can request the services and send inquiries.

Education

Software Engineer - Universidad Tecnológica Nacional.

Rosario, April 2014 - December 2018

Relevant coursework: Data Mining, Algorithms and Web Development.

Cambridge English First Certificate - IATEL

Rosario Grade B

Languages

Spanish - native.

English - fluent, full professional proficiency.